You never know what secrets your loved ones may be hiding.
Come to Daddy is a comedy, horror, mystery film directed by Ant Timpson.
After receiving a cryptic letter from his estranged father, Norval travels to his
dad’s oceanfront home for what he hopes will be a positive experience.
If only he’d known the dark truth about his old man beforehand.
Norval Greenwood, played by Elijah Wood.
Gordon, played by Stephen McHattie.
Jethro, played by Michael Smiley.
Gladys, played by Madeleine Sami.
Brian, played by Martin Donovan.
Precious, played by Ona Grauer.
Come to Daddy is a 2019 black comedy film directed by
Ant Timpson and written by Toby Harvard.
The film explores themes of affectation, torture,
beach house, crossbow, isolated house.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and dark.